彩色摄像机在功能上等同于我们所拥有的锥体系统
Color cameras are functionally equivalent to the system of cones that we have in the
我们眼睛的视网膜。
retinas of our eye.
来自场景的入射光通过透镜聚焦到人造视网膜上。
Incoming light from the scene is focused by a lens onto an artificial retina.
该人造视网膜包括硅光传感器阵列。
This artificial retina comprises an array of silicon photo sensors.
这些是测量入射光量的固态电路。
These are solid state circuits that measure the amount of incoming light.
它们实际上对相当广泛的光线敏感。
They are actually sensitive to quite a broad spectrum of light.
因此，为了使它们对颜色敏感，我们在这些硅传感器上印刷单独的颜色
So to make them color sensitive we print on top of these silicon sensors individual color
我们打印红色，绿色和蓝色滤镜图案的滤镜。
filters where we print patterns of red, green and blue filters.
这使得单独的硅光电传感器能够测量其数量
This gives the individual silicon photo sensor then the ability to measure the amount of
在人造视网膜上的特定点处进入红色，绿色或蓝色光。
incoming red, green or blue light at that particular point on the artificial retina.
大多数彩色相机使用一系列颜色过滤器，看起来像这样。
Most color cameras use an array of color filters that looks something like this.
这种滤色器模式通常被称为拜耳滤波器阵列，并且是
This pattern of color filters is frequently referred to as a Bayer filter array, and is
以布莱斯拜耳的名字命名，他于1976年发明了这种想法。
named after Bryce Bayer who invented this idea way back in 1976.
拜耳滤波器的基本元素是两个两个网格，它包含两个绿色
The fundamental element in the Bayer filter is a two by two grid and it contains two green
过滤一个红色滤镜和一个蓝色滤镜。
filters one red filter and one blue filter.
出于示例的目的，假设每个底层光传感器正在返回
For the purpose of example, imagine that each of the underlying photo sensors is returning
这些特定值和这些是无符号的八位整数，它们之间有所不同
these particular values and these are unsigned eight bit integer numbers which vary between
0和255。
0 and 255.
而且，让我们考虑一下我们想要测量红色，绿色和蓝色的数量
And further, let’s consider we want to measure the amount of red, green and blue at this
特别关注人造视网膜。
particular point on the artificial retina.
那么红色的答案非常清楚，此时红色的数量是75，它
Well the answer for red is really pretty clear, the amount of red at this point is 75, it
是光线通过覆盖后光电传感器返回的光线
is what is being returned by the photo sensor after the light has passed through the overlying
红色滤镜。
red filter.
但现在让我们说我想知道这个特定位置的绿灯数量
But let’s say now that I want to know the amount of green light at this particular location
这是有问题的，因为这个特殊的传感器上有一个红色的过滤器
and that is problematic because this particular sensor has got a red filter on it there is
我无法测量那里的绿光量，因为有一个红色滤光片
no way that I can measure the amount of green light there because there is a red filter
不是绿色过滤器。
not a green filter.
现在我们所做的只是平均所有邻居的绿色价值，我们说
Now what we do is simply average the green value of all of the neighbours and we say
这是圈出像素的绿光量的良好近似值。
that this is a good approximation to the amount of green light at the pixel that is circled.
同样，如果你想测量这个特定像素的蓝光量我们
Similarly, if you want to measure the amount of blue light at this particular pixel we
取相邻蓝色像素的平均值。
take the average of the neighbouring blue pixels.
因此，对于此阵列中的每个像素，我们可以直接测量一种颜色，我们可以估计两种颜色
So for every pixel in this array we can measure directly one color and we can estimate two
邻居的其他颜色。
other colors from its neighbours.
如果我们的传感器是NxM像素阵列，那么我们可以估计红色，绿色和蓝色值
If our sensor is an NxM pixel array, then we can estimate the red, green and blue values
每个像素。
of every pixel.
这意味着我们从这个人工视网膜返回的总共3xNxM值。
That means than we have a total of 3xNxM values returned from this artificial retina.
但实际上只进行了NxM实际测量。
But in reality there are only NxM actual measurements being made.
只有很多单独的光传感器。
There are only that many individual photo sensors.
剩下的价值已经估算完了。
The rest of the values have been estimated.
因此，另一种方法是存储由照片直接测量的值
So an alternative approach is just to store the values directly measured by the photo
传感器-NxM值-然后还要注意滤色器的属性
sensors — the NxM value — and then also take note of the properties of the color filters
与不同像素相关联的这是另一种表示方式
that are associated with the different pixels and this is an alternative way of representing
图像和这被称为原始图像文件格式。
the image and this is referred to as a raw image file format.
它与普通的红色，绿色和蓝色图像不同。
It is different to a normal red, green and blue image.
我们需要做一些后期处理;我们需要应用过滤器的特性
We need to do some post processing; we need to apply the characteristics of the filters
在相机中存储在文件中的数据。
in the camera to the data that is stored within the file.